

# LINDSAY FORRISTER

Web Developer/Designer

E. lindsayforrister@gmail.com | T. 678.447.9115

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/lindsayforrister

Portfolio: lindsayforrister.squarespace.com | Github: github.com/lforrister

As a front end web developer with a background in art direction and graphic design, I am committed to creating work that provides a high quality experience, both in aesthetic and functionality.

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Adobe Photoshop | Adobe Illustrator | Adobe InDesign | Sketch | InVision | HTML5 CSS | Bootstrap | Javascript | jQuery | Node.js | MySQL | AJAX | APIs | JSON | Express

#### **EDUCATION**

#### SOUTHERN METHODIST UNIVERSITY

April 2017 - October 2017

SMU Coding Bootcamp - Full Stack Web Development

An extensive 24-week long boot camp dedicated to designing and building web applications.

Applications Built:

PLUG IN: A web application that allowed users to search for music events in their area using the Eventful API.

- I was responsible for the front end development & UX/UI of the project through the use of HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Javascript & JQuery.
- I was responsible for implementing the Google Maps API, which connected to our Firebase database in order to retrieve the user's selected information.

## SOUTHERN METHODIST UNIVERSITY

August 2012 - May 2016 B.A. Advertising; B.A. Music; Minor in Graphic Design Cum. GPA: 3.86 Accolades:

- Graduated Cum Laude • Provost Scholarship Recipient
- Member of Kappa Tau Alpha Honors Society

#### RELEVANT WORK EXPERIENCE

**CORE PUBLISHING** June 2016 - Present

Art Director

- Responsible for the editorial design of Dallas Hotel Magazine, Houston Hotel Magazine, Denver Hotel Magazine & Colorado Hotel Magazine.
- Responsible for the design of marketing materials.
- Maintained/updated digital materials, including dallashotelmagazine.com and Core Publishing's social media accounts.

### FREELANCE DESIGNER

January 2015 - Present

• Worked with clients such as Attraction Lab, Russ Lyon | Sotheby's International Realty, Dexter & Company, and Not On My Campus to provide polished graphics for print and digital platforms.